Mss.B.H357.p
American Philosophical Society
- I. Correspondence
  - National Social Welfare Assembly
  - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness
  - National Society of Caterers to Industry
  - National Society of Crippled Children and Adults, Inc.
  - National Tuberculosis Association.
  - National Union of Manufacturers
  - National Venereal Disease Committee
  - National Vitamin Foundation, Inc.
  - Nattress, W E
  - Nau, Carl A
  - Near East College Associates
  - Needham, R A
  - Neff, E
  - Neighborhood Health Development, Inc.
  - NeJames, Wadih
  - Nelson Company
  - Nelson, Arvid, J
  - Nelson, David H
  - Nelson, Thomas H
  - Neptune Meter Co.
  - Neuberger & Berman
  - Neumann, Martin
  - Neville, Herbert C
  - Neviskillen, Countess of
  - New England Steamship Co.
  - New Guinea. Department of Public Health
  - New Jersey College for women
  - New Jersey Manufacturers Association
  - New Jersey. Commissioner of Education
  - New Jersey. Department of Health
  - New Jersey. Home Economics Department of Health
  - New Masses
  - New State School for the Blind
  - New York (State). Commissioner of Motor Vehicles
  - New York (State). Committee on Tuberculosis and Public Health
  - New York (State). Department of Labor
  - New York (State). Department of Taxation and Finance
  - New York (State). Income Tax Bureau
  - New York (State). Joint Legislative Commission on Education
  - New York (State). Joint Legislative Commission on Nutrition
  - New York (State). Joint Legislative Commission on Problems of the Aging
  - New York Academy of Medicine
  - New York Academy of Sciences
  - New York Athletic Club
  - New York Bank for Savings
  - New York Central RR
  - New York City Cancer Committee
  - New York City, Commissioner of Health
  - New York City, Department of Health
  - New York City. POLICE Department
  - New York Committee of the National War Fund
  - New York Community Trust
  - New York County Clerk
  - New York Herald Tribune
  - New York Institute of Dietetics
  - New York Journal American
  - New York Library Association
  - New York Magazines
  - New York Mirror
  - New York Naval Shipyard
  - New York Post-Graduate Medical School and Hospital
  - New York Society of Tropical Medicine
  - New York State Health Insurance
  - New York State Journal of Medicine
  - New York State Optometric Association
  - New York State Senate
  - New York State Society of Industrial Medicine, Inc.
  - New York State. Department of Health
  - New York Telephone Company
  - New York Times.
  - New York Tuberculosis and Health Association
  - New York University Dinner
  - New York War Fund
  - New York World's Fair
  - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railway Co.
  - New York. Conference of Medical Officers of State Department of Health, July, 1911
  - New Zeland.Department of Public Health
  - Newburger, Morris
  - Newell, Mrs. J P
  - Newell-Emmett Co., Inc.
  - Newsweek (magazine).
  - Newton, Mrs. J
  - Newton, Richard
  - Ngata, Sir Apirana
  - Nichols, Jack
  - Nichols, Raymond
  - Noah, Nathan O
  - Nogrady, Georges L
  - Nolan, Dennis E
  - Norfolk Shipbuilding and Drydock Corp.
  - Norin, Jean D
  - Normanly, John F
  - Norris, Howes Jr.
  - North American Cement Corporation
  - North American Film Corp.
  - North Carolina Industrial Commission
  - North Carolina. State Commission for the Blind
  - North Shore Health Resort, Winnetka, Illinois
  - Northam Warren Corp.
  - Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Company
  - Northwestern University Medical School
  - Norton Grinding Wheel Co.
  - Norton, Clement A
  - Norton, Mrs.
  - Norton, W.W. and Company, Incorporated
  - Noyes & Sproul, Inc.
  - Noyes, Alice M
  - Nurses Counseling and Placement Service
  - Nutrition Foundation, Inc.
  - Nyman, John Egbert
  - O"Keefe, W J
  - Oak, Dorothy
  - Oakland (Cal.) Forum
  - Oaks, L Robert
  - Oaranirem Oeter
  - Oberlaender Trust
  - O'Brien, C F
  - O'Brien, Evelyn
  - O'Brien, Henry R
  - O'Brien, Marie Beyer
  - Occupational Hazards, Inc.
  - Occupational Index, Inc.
  - O'Connor, F W
  - O'Connor, Frank D
  - O'Connor, Frank P.
  - O'Connor, Mary Wistar
  - Odenatt,W Burrill
  - Odenweller, Helen
  - Odom, Mrs. A E
  - O'Donnell, George A
  - Office of Defense Health and Welfare Services
  - Office of Industrial Health
  - Office of War INformation
  - Ogata, Teruko
  - Ogilvie, Jessie Kerr
  - O'Hara, Joseph
  - O'Hara, Robert Owen
  - Ohio Pure Food Company
  - Ohio. Department of Health
  - Old American Insurance Company
  - Old Beach Hotel
  - Old South Association in Boston
  - Oldbury Electro-Chemical Co.
  - Oldenbourg, Joachim
  - Oldham, Mrs. George A
  - Oldt, Frank
  - Olin, J D
  - Oliver Iron and Steel Corp.
  - Oliver,Wade
  - Olson, Mfg. Co.
  - Onorato, Michael P
  - Opdyke, William K
  - Ophthalmological Foundation, Inc.
  - Ophuls, Fred
  - Opie, Eugene Lindsay
  - Oppenheim, Edward E
  - Oral Hygiene Committee of Greater New York
  - Order of Adventurers
  - Ordway, Thomas
  - Oregon State College
  - Orenstein, A J
  - Oriental Medical Association
  - O'Rourke, Leata Decker
  - Orth, Charles D
  - Ortiz, Alfredo
  - Osborn, Frederick
    See: Galton Society, in:
  - Osborn, M J
  - Osborne, Edith W (Mrs. Charles D)
  - Oshima, T
  - Ossipoff, Michael
  - Ostrow, Alexander L
  - Oswald, Richard
  - Otis Elevator Co.
  - Ott, Jacqueline
  - Ottofy, Louis
  - Oursler, Fulton
  - OuYang, George H
  - Ovex Chemical Co., Inc.
  - Oviatt, Sidney
  - Owen, Annie R C
  - Owen, Gilbert R
  - Owen, Neil W
  - Owen, Ward E
  - Owens, James G
  - Owens-Illinois Glass Co.
  - Oxford University Press
  - Oxley, Victoria A
  - Ozsgyani, Bela
  - Pacific Industrial Hygiene & Research Foundation
  - Pack, William F
  - Packard, Donn
  - Packard, Francis R
  - Packwood, G. H. Mfg. Co.
  - Page, Gertrude W
  - Page, John P
  - Page, Robert Collier
  - Paget, F A
  - Paine, Ruth
  - Pakas, Manfred A
  - Pala, Saturnino Corro
  - Palace Hotel, San Francisco
  - Palacio, Carlos A
  - Palanca, Jose Alberto
  - Palmer House
  - Palmer, Eric Harold
  - Palmer, Lilla
  - Palmer, Mrs. E
  - Palmer, Rachel M
  - Pan American Medical Association
  - Pan American Sanitary Bureau
  - Panama canal. Chief of Office
  - PanAmerican World Airways
  - Paniello, Francois
  - Paper Cup & Container Institute
  - Parham, Harry J
  - Park, H B
  - Park, Julian
  - Parker, Ada Dorr
  - Parker, Phyllis
  - Parker-Kalon Corp.
  - Parkinson, Stanley R.
  - Parlett, Robert C
  - Parmenter, M D
  - Parmentier, Douglas
  - Parr, Leland W
  - Parran, Thomas H, de
  - Parry, R H
  - Parsons, Walter Stanley
  - Partee, W T
  - Pasewalk, Leo
  - Pasquarelli, Josephine
  - Passano, L Magruder
  - Passow-Kernen, Hilde
  - Paternoster, A
  - Paterson, Amy
  - Pathe, Gorges
  - Paton, Francis D
  - Patricia, Sister M Joan
  - Patrick, Agnes C
  - Patterson, Ross V
  - Patton, Hiram H
  - Patton, L B
  - Paul, George P
  - Paul, John R
  - Paul, John R
  - Peabody, George Foster
  - Peacock, Kenneth C
  - Pearce, R M
  - Pearl, Raymond
  - Pearson, John
  - Pearson, Maurice G
  - Pearson, MILO L, Jr.
  - Peavy, Wilson Lumber Co.
  - Pedrick, Mary Knox
  - Pelham Stationers, Inc.
  - Pemberton House, Inc.
  - Pena, Alfonso De La
  - Pengranse, Ed L
  - Penn Mental Corp. of Pennsylvania
  - Penn Mutual Life Insurance Company.
  - Penney, J C
  - Penniman, Christine B
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Company
  - Pennsylvania Society
  - Pennsylvania State Association of Master Plumbers
  - Pennsylvania Tuberculosis Society.
  - Pennsylvania. Department of Health
  - Pennsylvania. Department of Labor and Industry
  - Pentner, J H
  - People's National Health Comm.
  - Peoples' Press
  - Peoria Municipal Tuberculosis Sanitarium
  - Pepper, Claude
  - Pepsi-Cola Co.
  - Pepsodent Co.
  - Perfect Circle Co.
  - Perkins, Phyllis Hammond
  - Perkins, W H
  - Perkins, William Hervey
  - Perlman, Henrietta
  - Perrin, Marian T
  - Perron, Marius
  - Perry Aircraft Products Corp.
  - Perry, Ernestine
  - Perry, Robert
  - Perry, Victor Prittie
  - Perspectives in Biology and Medicine
  - Peter, William Wesley
  - Peters, John L
  - Peterson, Antoinette R
  - Peterson, E H
  - Peterson, Elsie G
  - Peterson, Frederick
  - Peterson, Gilly
  - Peterson, Mrs.
  - Peterson, Whitney
  - Pfizer International, Inc.
  - Pharmaceutical Organics, Inc., Third Annual Report
  - Phelps, Glenn H
  - Phelps, William Lyon
  - Phi Beta Kappa.
  - Philadelphia Electric Company
  - Philadelphia Safety Council
  - Philadelphia. Department of Public Health
  - Philippine Club
  - Philippine Islands Medical Ass'n
  - Philippine Islands, Govt. of. Bureau of Civil Service
  - Philippine Islands. Secretary of Health
  - Philippine Society of California
  - Philippine War Relief (of the U.S.) Inc.
  - Philippines, Republic of. Dept. of Health
  - Philipps, A H
  - Philips, Belle M
  - Phillips, Alfred N, Jr.
  - Phillips, Mrs. John M
  - Phillips, Richard
  - Phillips, Robert E
  - Philpot, Ethelyne Carter
  - Phinney, Charles H
  - Phosphor Bronze Smelting Co.
  - Physical Culture
  - Picking, H M
  - Pier, H W
  - Pierce, Edward Allen
  - Pierce, Mrs. W W
  - Pierce, Virginia
  - Pierson, H H
  - Pierson, Helen (Mrs. Lewis)
  - Pierson, Lewis
  - Pietrocovsky, M
  - Pilgrimage from Poverty
  - Pillsbury, Jane
  - Pinaberg, Sarah
  - Pinchot, Gifford
  - Pinckney, John J
  - Pinkham, Gertrude A
  - Pinks, F O
  - Pioneer Rubber Co.
  - Pioneers' Descendants. NSW (Australia) New Zealand
  - Piper, Mrs. W H
  - Pishney, Frances M
  - Pitfield, Robert L
  - Pitré, T P
  - Pittman, Vivian
  - Pittsburgh, University of. University Club
  - Pitzer, Margaret
  - Piva, John J, Jr.
  - Place, Edward R
  - Placement Agencies for Individual Health Personnel
  - Planned Parenthood Federation of America
  - Planned Parenthood League of Connecticut, Inc.
  - Platov, Elaine C
  - Platt, Florence F
  - Pleadwell, Frank L
  - Pledge for Peace Committee
  - Plesset, Isabel R
    See: Noguchi, Hideyo, in:
  - Podemsky, Ruda
  - Podiatry Society of the State of New York
  - Poe, Sophie
  - Pohl, Lucien L
  - Pohlman, Augustus Grote
  - Poland, Eleanor
  - Pollak, Franklin S
  - Pollak, Maxim
  - Pollock, A W
  - Polo, Duko de
  - Polygraphic Company of America
  - Pomeroy Tribune Telegraph
  - Pomrinse, Catherine
  - Pond, James B
  - Pool, Leila M
  - Pool, Mrs. Edward
  - Pool. Eugene H
  - Poor's Publishing Co.
  - Popular Mechanics
  - Portland Cement Association
  - Post Graduate Hospital
  - Post, Alice Hyde
  - Post, John
  - Poteet, Lillie Mae
  - Potsdamer, Joseph B
  - Potsdamer, Louis S
  - Pottenger, F M Jr.
  - Poulet, ACTON
  - Powell
  - Powers Regulator Co.
  - Powers, Clare
  - Prather, Mrs. E S
  - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft
  - Pratt, Dallas
  - Pratt-Whitney Co.
  - Prentice-Hall, Inc.
  - Prentiss, Mrs. Francis F
  - Pressed and Welded Steel Products Co., Inc.
  - Prest-O-Lite Co., Inc
  - Preston, T W
  - Pribeck, Walter H
  - Price Flavoring Extract Co.
  - Price, Derek J de Solla
  - Price, Elinor
  - Price, Leo
  - Price, Ray G
  - Prichard, Robert W
  - Pritchard, Stuart
  - Proctor, Eleanor S
  - Pro-Tex Process, Inc.
  - Provence-Jarrard Co., Inc.
  - Proximity Mfg. Co.
  - Prudden, Russell F
  - Public Health Committee of the Cup and Container Institute
  - Public Health Nursing Association of Pittsburgh, Pa., Inc.
  - Publishers Clearing House
  - Publishers Syndicate
  - Publishers" Weekly
  - Puliam, William E
  - Pullman Company
  - Punch, Delia
  - Purcell, Jan
  - Purdy, C
  - Pure Milk Association
  - Purviance, James N
  - Pusey, Leo Arthur
  - Pusey, William A
  - Putnam, Alfred
  - Putnam, Richard
  - Pyle, David H McAlpin
  - Pyrene Mfg. Co.
  - Quantuck Beach Club
  - Quast, E von
  - Queen's Hospital Honolulu
  - Quehl, Theodor
  - Quezon, Manuel
  - Quinn, Elizabeth
  - Quinton, Sidney
  - Radai, Thomas
  - Radio Corporation of America
  - Radio Station WCPO
  - Raftery, Edith
  - Ragan, Besse
  - Rager, Irene (Mrs. Homer)
  - Ragsdale, Mrs. Clifford
  - Railroad Journal
  - Raitt, Isabel
  - Raitt, John E
  - Rajchman, Ludwik
  - Ralston Purina Co.
  - Ramus, Carl
  - Rance, H C
  - Rand Mines, Ltd.
  - Rand, Frank H
  - Randall, Ethel
  - Randle, H G
  - Rankin, John H
  - Ransom, Mrs. Fred C
  - Ranum, Ida S
  - Rappaport, Irving
  - Rappleye, Willard C
  - Rarey, G H
  - Rasken, Nathan
  - Rath, Walter C
  - Ravenel, Mazyck P
  - Ray, Jacqueline
  - Ray, Lucy Taylor
  - Ray, Mrs. W T
  - Ray-O-Vac Company
  - Reader's Digest
  - Reading Club Members
  - Reading Hospital
  - Ready, Margaret R
  - Réalités
  - Reckefus, Charles H
  - Red Head Brand Co.
  - Red River Lumber Co.
  - Redmayne, Robert
  - Reed, C I
  - Reed, Elizabeth (Mrs. Charles S)
  - Reed, Florence H
  - Reed, Horace
  - Reed, Lowell J
  - Reed, Robert
  - Reeve, William
  - Reeves, Myrtle W
  - Regan, Rita
  - Reiber, Mrs. Frederick W
  - Reid, Mrs. Ogden
  - Reimann, Stanley P
  - Rein, Charles, Inc.
  - Reinhardt, Mary
  - Reinhart, Annie F
  - Reinhold, C H
  - Reisinger, Anna M
  - Rendall, Mrs. Allen
  - Renzetti, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph
  - Replogle, Blanche McMillen
  - Replogle, J Leonard
  - Report on the Properties of the Sonchiloa Mines Company
  - Resident Commissioner of the Philippines to the U. S.
  - Restaurant Price Branch
  - Reuther, Ida
  - Reyes, Guadalupe
  - Reynal & Hitchcock, Inc.
  - Reynolds Metal Co.
  - Reynolds, Frank W
  - Reynolds, Paul R. & Co.
  - Rice, John L
  - Richard, Charles B
  - Richards, Carol
  - Richards, John W
  - Richards, Sir Arthur Frederick
  - Richardson, Helene
  - Richmond, Verna
  - Ridgaway, Helen Lydia
  - Ridgway, M B
  - Riesman
  - Riggin, I C
  - Rimington, Critchell
  - Rischner, Joseph
  - Risley, Marius B
  - Rissler, Ross W
  - Ritter Company, Inc.
  - Ritz Hotel, Madrid, Paris
  - Rivers, William C
  - Riverside Church
  - RN Magazine
  - Robberson Steel Co.
  - Robbins Co.
  - Robbins, R
  - Roberts, Charles A
  - Roberts, Elta C
  - Roberts, Mrs. P
  - Roberts, Mrs. Walter E
  - Robertson
  - Robertson, A W
  - Robertson, Alexander J
  - Robertson, E
  - Robertson, Gordon
  - Robertson, John, Inc.
  - Robertson, William H
  - Robinson, Mrs. S M
  - Robinson, Samuel R
  - Robson, Thomas
  - Rochester (NY) Chamber of Commerce
  - Rochester Academy of Medicine
  - Rochester Ropes, Inc.
  - Rock, Joseph F
  - Rockefeller Foundation
  - Rockefeller, John D., III
  - Rockefeller, John D., Jr.
  - Rockwood, W M
  - Rocky Mountain Conference on Industrial Health
  - Roddy, Mabel E
  - Roddy, William F
  - Roebling, John A., Sons Co.
  - Roethig, Mrs. F J
  - Roffey Park Rehabilitation Centre
  - Rogers, A J
  - Rogers, Burton
  - Rogers, Charlotte A
  - Rogers, Miriam
  - Rogers, W E
  - Rohess, Karl
  - Rome, Mrs. Samuel
  - Roon, Karin
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas
  - Roosevelt, Theodore
  - Roper, Daniel G
  - Roper, Kenneth L
  - Rose, Howard Wickliffe
  - Rose, Wickliffe, International Health Board
  - Rosebury, Theodor
  - Rosenberg, L
  - Rosenfeld, Milton A
  - Rosenthal, Bessie L
  - Rosenthal, J
  - Rosenthal, M
  - Rosenthal, Sigismund
  - Rosicrucian Order
  - Rosner, Lorraine
  - Ross, Emily
  - Ross, Emory
  - Ross, Helen
  - Ross, James
  - Ross, Mrs. James
  - Rossiter, P S
  - Rotan, Mrs. George V
  - Rotary Club of Johnstown, Pa.
  - Rotary Club of Lancaster, Pa.
  - Roth, Sidney A
  - Rothen, Mrs. W H
  - Rothen, Roberta
  - Rothman, H N
  - Rowe, George S
  - Rowell, "Mayme" (Mrs. Geoge A)
  - Roy, James A
  - Royer, B Franklin
  - Rubenstein, Michael H
  - Rubenstein, Mrs. Charles
  - Rubin, Hans
  - Rublee, Juliet Barrett
    See: Sanger, Margaret, in:
  - Ruby, Florence
  - Rude, Evelyn
  - Rudisill, Earl S
  - Rudkin, Mrs. Henry A
  - Rugger, F E
  - Ruggles, Jessie M
  - Rumbaugh, James H
  - Rumely, Edward A
  - Rusby, H H
  - Rush, Annette J
  - Rush, Norman J
  - Rushnen, Barbara
  - Rusk, Dean
  - Rusk, Howard A
  - Ruskin, Mrs.
  - Ruskin, Simon
  - Russell, A j H
  - Russell, Elma Gaines
  - Russell, F F
  - Russell, Paul F
  - Russell, Phyllis A
  - Russell, Sir Alexander
  - Russell, Thomas H
  - Russell, Walter R
  - Ruthenberg, Louis
  - Ruutz-Rees, Caroline
  - Ruz Llanos, F
  - Ryan, Georgina A
  - Ryder, Mrs. Charles E
  - Sabin, Elizabeth
  - Sachigo River Exploration Co., Ltd.
  - Sachritz, Irvin
  - Safety Research Institute, Inc.
  - Safford, Victor
  - Saiki, Tadasu
  - Sailliard, J H
  - Saint Luke's Hospital, Manila
  - Salmon, David R
  - Salmon, Henry
  - Salsbury, C G
  - Salter, Lawrence C
  - Salvation Army
  - Salvi, Junio
  - Sample, N W Jr.
  - Sampson, W
  - Samras, Evelyn K
  - San Antonio Drug Co.
  - San Diego (Cal.) Public Library
  - San Francisco Tuberculosis Association
  - San Francisco, City and County, Department of Public Health
  - Sanborn, Mary Anderson
  - Sanctum
  - Sanctum, of Litchfield, Conn., Constitution
  - Sanderson, MRS. James
  - Sandler, Benjamin P
  - Sands, Harry
  - Sanford, Conley H
  - Sanford, Mary B
  - Sanford, Walter S
  - Sanger, W T
  - Santa Eulalia, Barcelona
  - Sante Fe Coast Lines Hospital Association
  - Santiago, Elroy
  - Santoire, Henri
  - Sappington, C O
  - Sappington, Emmet Earl
  - Sargent, Noel
  - Sargent, Porter
  - Saturday Evening Post
  - Saturday Night Press
  - Saturday Review of Literature
  - Saunders, George M
  - Saunders, W. B., Co.
  - Sawyer, Elizabeth W
  - Sawyer, George L
  - Sawyer, W A
  - Sawyer, Wilbur A
  - Schaffer, T W
  - Schaffner, R Adele
  - Schapiro, Mark M
  - Schapiro, Matilde M
  - Schapiro, Mrs. Louis
  - Scharff, J W
  - Scharmer, Bernice
  - Scheller, Samuel & Co.
  - Schenck, Douglas S
  - Schenley Hotel
  - Schenley Laboratories, Inc.
  - Schepp, William J
  - Scherer, Mrs. Edward
  - Scherer, Simon C
  - Schick, Alice
  - Schieble, Mrs. Isabel O
  - Schieffelin, William Jay
  - Schill, George
  - Schill, Jean (Mrs. George)
  - Schilling, Irene
  - Schillo, Mrs. Paul
  - Schlansky, H P
  - Schleuder, H W
  - Schlitz Brewing Co.
  - Schlitz Brewing Co.
  - Schlotzhauer, Mrs. Carl A
  - Schmidt, D
  - Schmidt, W D
  - Schmincke, Mildred
  - Schnabel, T G
  - Schneider, Harold W
  - Schnur, Leo
  - Schofield, Lemuel B
  - Schrader's A., Son
  - Schramm, Elizabeth E
  - Schroeder, Ilse
  - Schueller, Hugo
  - Schuetze, Philip L
  - Schüfner, W
  - Schultz, Mrs. P
  - Schuman, Henry, Inc., Publishers
  - Schwab, L S
  - Schwartz, Charles L
  - Schwartz, Luois P
  - Schwartz, Sam
  - Schwing, Karl
  - Science
  - Science Service
  - Scientific Nutrition Corp.
  - Scochman, Donald
  - Scott, Ann
  - Scott, Edgar
  - Scott, Elizabeth
  - Scott, George Dow
  - Scott, John G
  - Scott, Winifred B
  - Scoullar Co., Ltd.
  - Scoville, Genevieve
  - Scudder, Bradford C
  - Seaman, Mrs. Georgie M
  - Searcher, Victor
  - Searcher, Victor and Madeleine
  - Searle, Bess Madge Caldwell
  - Seel, W E
  - Seeley, L E
  - Segal, Henry Hillson
  - Seipt, Irene S
  - Selby
  - Selden, Robert H
  - Selig, Lester
  - Seligman, Walter
  - Seltz, Lucile
  - Selwyn Clarke, P S
  - Selz, Frank E
  - Selz, Lucille (Mrs. Frank)
  - Semmes, John E
  - Semple, D
  - Sen, Gertrude E
  - Senton, Thelma
  - Servel, Inc.
  - Settergren, Marguerite
  - Sevin, Gertrude K
  - Sexias, Marjorie C
  - Seydall, Mildred
  - Shackelford, J Hinton
  - Shackelford, John W
  - Shafer, Donald M
  - Shafer, J M
  - Shaffer, Philip A
  - Shallow, Thomas A
  - Shanks Metal Products Co.
  - Shannon, John T
  - Shaper, James P
  - Shapiro, Gertrude G
  - Shapiro, Samuel & Co.
  - Sharp & Dohme
  - Sharp, W D
  - Shastid, T H
  - Shatluck, George C
  - Shaver, C L
  - Shawkey, Eloise
  - Shearer, Grace Longley
  - Shearson, Hammill & Co.
  - Sheifly, John E
  - Shelby,C L
  - Shepard, Kate A
  - Shepard, William P
  - Sherfessee, Forsythe W
  - Sherman, William O'Neill
  - Shewan, D R
  - Shields, Marjorie G
  - Shifferstine, Edgar E
  - Shinmoto, George
  - Shipler, Guy Emery
  - Shirk, Katherine
  - Shoemaker, Mrs. Murray M
  - Shope, Eleanor H
  - Shortt, H E
  - Shostac, Frances
  - Shrawder, Jean
  - Shuk, Lajos
  - Shulton, Richard A
  - Sideli, A M
  - Siegfried, Sidney
  - Sieskind, Richard
  - Sikorsky Aircraft
  - Silverman, Max K
  - Silverstein, Ruth
  - Simmonds, Nina
  - Simmons, James Stevens
  - Simmons, R. F., Co.
  - Simmons, Virgil
  - Simon, Mrs. L K
  - Simon, Richard L
  - Simonds Saw and Steel Co.
  - Simons, Donald J
  - Simons, George W
  - Simonson, Ernst
  - Simonson, Lee
  - Simpich, Frederick
  - Simplex Wire and Cable Co.
  - Simpson, Harold N
  - Sims, L P
  - Sinclair Oil Co.
  - Sinclair, Penfield
  - Singapore Mutiny
  - Singer, Shirley
  - Sinnott, Margaret B
  - Sinton, J A
  - Sisk, Henry L
  - Siskind, Janet
  - Sison, Antonio
  - Skouras, Spyros P
  - Slagle, Olive
  - Slappey, Mrs. George H
  - Slater Systems, Inc.
  - Slattery, Gertrude Quinn
  - Slee, Anne Benoist
  - Sloan, Mary N
  - Slominski, A
  - Slotnik, Lawrence
  - Smallpox Vaccine, Island of Caluya
  - Smith, E B
  - Smith, Emily C
  - Smith, Freemont
  - Smith, H W
  - Smith, Harry C
  - Smith, Howard
  - Smith, Hugh H
  - Smith, Irving W
  - Smith, J Russell
  - Smith, J W
  - Smith, James M
  - Smith, Juthia Stuart
  - Smith, Kendrick
  - Smith, Nettie Wing
  - Smith, Thur
  - Smolka, Leo
  - Snap-on-Tools Corp.
  - Sneath, P A T
  - Snow, Daniel C
  - Snow, Ronald L
  - Snow, William F
  - Snyder, Laurence H
  - Soames, Marion
  - Social Security Administration
  - Socialized Medicine
  - Société de Marie
  - Society for Seamen's Children
  - Society for the Prevention of Asphyxial Death, Inc.
  - Society of Pennsylvania Women in NY
  - Society of Recreation Workers of America
  - Society of St. Johnsland.
  - Solins, Samuel
  - Sonn, Eric
  - Sonneborn, L., Sons, Inc.
  - Sonoco Products Co.
  - Sorabje, Cornelia
  - Sormani, E J Jr.
  - Sote, Elizabeth
  - Soule, Malcolm H
  - South Carolina Public Service Authority
  - South Carolina. State Board of Health
  - South, Roy
  - Southwood, A R
  - Spalding, Mary L
  - Special Libraries Association
  - Speller, Robert, & Sons, Publishers
  - Spencer Chemical Company
  - Spencer, Mrs. Cornelia J
  - Spencer, R R
  - Spencer-Mead, Inc.
  - Sperry, Mrs. Roger
  - Sperry-Gyroscope Co.
  - Spiegel, Herbert
  - Spies, Bruno M
  - Spies, Thomas D
  - Spiro, William
  - Sprawson, C A
  - Spring, Lynn
  - Spring,Florence J
  - Springfield (Mass.), Union
  - Sprout, Waldron & Co., Inc.
  - Squires, E M
  - St. Barnabas Hospital
  - St. Joseph County (Ind.) Anti-Tuberculosis League
  - Stack, Herbert J
  - Stahly, Inc.
  - Staight, Marjorie
  - Staley, Anna M
  - Standard Brands, Inc.
  - Standard Oil Company of Ohio
  - Standard Railway Sanitary Code
  - Stanford, E E
  - Stanoyevich, Mrs. B S
  - Stanton, Sir Thomas
  - Starr, Thomas J
  - State Mutual Life Assurance Co. of Worcester
  - Statler Hotel
  - Stearns and Foster.
  - Stearns, Emily St. Agnan
  - Steel Plate Fabricators Association
  - Steffens, Ralph
  - Stein, Bruno
  - Stein, Elizabeth
  - Stein, Fritz
  - Stein, Jeannette B
  - Stein, Mrs. Abe
  - Steindorff, Claire
  - Steiner, Eugen
  - Steiner, Fay
  - Steinhaus, Arthur H
  - Steinhof, Giuseppe
  - Stender, Lois (Mrs. Charles A)
  - Stephenson, C S
  - Stern, Mrs. Marvin L
  - Sterner, Louise E
  - Stetten, Dewitt
  - Stettinius, E R Jr.
  - Stevens, Arnold G
  - Stevens, Bruce
  - Stevens, Emma W
  - Stevens, Helen V
  - Stevens, Lewis M
  - Stevenson, John E
  - Stewart, A D
  - Stewart, De Lisle
  - Stewart, George A
  - Stewart, P
  - Stickel, J F
  - Stillman, Maynard & Co.
  - Stimpson, E. B. Co.
  - Stimson, Barbara B
  - Stock, Margie
  - Stockton, John M
  - Stockwall, Frances
  - Stockwell, John W
  - Stockwell, Martha
  - Stohl, E L
  - Stokes, Frederick A., Co.
  - Stokes, Joseph D
  - Stoll, Mrs. Norman R
  - Stoll, Norman R
  - Stone, Hayden
  - Stone, John K P
  - Stone, Marian H
  - Stonebraker, Dalby
  - Stott, Mrs. J M
  - Stout, Wesley W
  - Stover, Blanche F
  - Straight, John Hawthorne